Friday, October 4 2024

Latest

* [OpenAI just raised $6.6bn in funding, but it drove a hard bargain – investors will be stopped from funding rivals](https://digitpatrox.com/openai-just-raised-6-6bn-in-funding-but-it-drove-a-hard-bargain-investors-will-be-stopped-from-funding-rivals/)
* [How to Improve Your Digital Transformation Project Failure Rate](https://digitpatrox.com/how-to-improve-your-digital-transformation-project-failure-rate/)
* [NYT Connections today hints and answers — Friday, October 4 (#481)](https://digitpatrox.com/nyt-connections-today-hints-and-answers-friday-october-4-481/)
* [Recently patched CUPS flaw can be used to amplify DDoS attacks](https://digitpatrox.com/recently-patched-cups-flaw-can-be-used-to-amplify-ddos-attacks/)
* [The new Ford Expedition adds Android Automotive and half of the Lincoln’s panoramic screen](https://digitpatrox.com/the-new-ford-expedition-adds-android-automotive-and-half-of-the-lincolns-panoramic-screen/)
* [Samsung One UI 7 Set to Release Next Year, Alongside Galaxy S25 Series](https://digitpatrox.com/samsung-one-ui-7-set-to-release-next-year-alongside-galaxy-s25-series/)
* [Software engineers are in for a rough ride as AI adoption ramps up – 80% will be forced to upskill by 2027 as the profession is transformed](https://digitpatrox.com/software-engineers-are-in-for-a-rough-ride-as-ai-adoption-ramps-up-80-will-be-forced-to-upskill-by-2027-as-the-profession-is-transformed/)
* [The EU wants to know more about social media algorithms – Computerworld](https://digitpatrox.com/the-eu-wants-to-know-more-about-social-media-algorithms-computerworld/)

[Home](https://digitpatrox.com/)_/_Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

At digitpatrox, accessible from www.digitpatrox.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by digitpatrox and how we use it.  
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.  
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in digitpatrox. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.  
Consent  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.  
Information we collect  
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.  
If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.  
When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.  
How we use your information  
We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

Provide, operate, and maintain our webste  
Improve, personalize, and expand our webste  
Understand and analyze how you use our webste  
Develop new products, services, features, and functionality  
Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the webste, and for marketing and promotional purposes  
Send you emails  
Find and prevent fraud

Log Files  
digitpatrox follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information. Our Privacy Policy was created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator and the Online Privacy Policy Generator.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
Like any other website, digitpatrox uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.  
For more general information on cookies, please read “What Are Cookies”.  
Our Advertising Partners  
Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.  
Advertising Partners Privacy Policies  
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of digitpatrox.  
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on digitpatrox, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.  
Note that digitpatrox has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
Third Party Privacy Policies  
digitpatrox’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.  
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)  
Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:  
Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.  
Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.  
Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.  
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.  
GDPR Data Protection Rights  
We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:  
The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.  
The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.  
The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.  
The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.  
The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.  
The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.  
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.  
Children’s Information  
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.  
digitpatrox does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.  

Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at digitpatrox@gmail.com

\-Digitpatrox

Popular Posts

    [iPhone 16 mass production begins, and it’s packing a new display — here’s what we know](https://digitpatrox.com/iphone-16-mass-production-begins-and-its-packing-a-new-display-heres-what-we-know/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    [Vonage Business Communications Review (2024): Is It Worth It?](https://digitpatrox.com/vonage-business-communications-review-2024-is-it-worth-it/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    August 13, 2024

    [FBI disrupts the Dispossessor ransomware operation, seizes servers](https://digitpatrox.com/fbi-disrupts-the-dispossessor-ransomware-operation-seizes-servers/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    [Indiana Jones The Great Circle Is Here with a Release Date and a PS5 Launch](https://digitpatrox.com/indiana-jones-the-great-circle-is-here-with-a-release-date-and-a-ps5-launch/)
    
    August 21, 2024

    [iPhone 16 mass production begins, and it’s packing a new display — here’s what we know](https://digitpatrox.com/iphone-16-mass-production-begins-and-its-packing-a-new-display-heres-what-we-know/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    [Vonage Business Communications Review (2024): Is It Worth It?](https://digitpatrox.com/vonage-business-communications-review-2024-is-it-worth-it/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    August 13, 2024

    [FBI disrupts the Dispossessor ransomware operation, seizes servers](https://digitpatrox.com/fbi-disrupts-the-dispossessor-ransomware-operation-seizes-servers/)
    
    August 13, 2024

    [Indiana Jones The Great Circle Is Here with a Release Date and a PS5 Launch](https://digitpatrox.com/indiana-jones-the-great-circle-is-here-with-a-release-date-and-a-ps5-launch/)
    
    August 21, 2024

    [OpenAI just raised $6.6bn in funding, but it drove a hard bargain – investors will be stopped from funding rivals](https://digitpatrox.com/openai-just-raised-6-6bn-in-funding-but-it-drove-a-hard-bargain-investors-will-be-stopped-from-funding-rivals/)
    
    4 mins ago

    [How to Improve Your Digital Transformation Project Failure Rate](https://digitpatrox.com/how-to-improve-your-digital-transformation-project-failure-rate/)
    
    8 mins ago

    [NYT Connections today hints and answers — Friday, October 4 (#481)](https://digitpatrox.com/nyt-connections-today-hints-and-answers-friday-october-4-481/)
    
    24 mins ago

    [Recently patched CUPS flaw can be used to amplify DDoS attacks](https://digitpatrox.com/recently-patched-cups-flaw-can-be-used-to-amplify-ddos-attacks/)
    
    52 mins ago
    
* [/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25656820/All_New_202025_20Ford_20Expedition_Platinum_20Ultimate_04.jpg)](https://digitpatrox.com/the-new-ford-expedition-adds-android-automotive-and-half-of-the-lincolns-panoramic-screen/)
    
    [The new Ford Expedition adds Android Automotive and half of the Lincoln’s panoramic screen](https://digitpatrox.com/the-new-ford-expedition-adds-android-automotive-and-half-of-the-lincolns-panoramic-screen/)
    
    1 hour ago

Digitpatrox will show you best Career and Income Sources and also present you Latest News around the globe in your finger tips.

Recent Topics

* [4 mins ago
    
    ### OpenAI just raised $6.6bn in funding, but it drove a hard bargain – investors will be stopped from funding rivals](https://digitpatrox.com/openai-just-raised-6-6bn-in-funding-but-it-drove-a-hard-bargain-investors-will-be-stopped-from-funding-rivals/)
* [8 mins ago
    
    ### How to Improve Your Digital Transformation Project Failure Rate](https://digitpatrox.com/how-to-improve-your-digital-transformation-project-failure-rate/)
* [24 mins ago
    
    ### NYT Connections today hints and answers — Friday, October 4 (#481)](https://digitpatrox.com/nyt-connections-today-hints-and-answers-friday-october-4-481/)

Most Popular Topics

* [August 26, 2024
    
    ### Apple Announces September 9 Event to Unveil iPhone 16 Series](https://digitpatrox.com/apple-announces-september-9-event-to-unveil-iphone-16-series/)
* [August 14, 2024
    
    ### Microsoft to archive unlicensed OneDrive business accounts, charge reactivation fee – Computerworld](https://digitpatrox.com/microsoft-to-archive-unlicensed-onedrive-business-accounts-charge-reactivation-fee-computerworld/)
* [August 21, 2024
    
    ### Use Automations to Keep Alarms From Going Off When You Don’t Need Them](https://digitpatrox.com/use-automations-to-keep-alarms-from-going-off-when-you-dont-need-them/)

Last Modified Topics

* [3 hours ago
    
    ### Software engineers are in for a rough ride as AI adoption ramps up – 80% will be forced to upskill by 2027 as the profession is transformed](https://digitpatrox.com/software-engineers-are-in-for-a-rough-ride-as-ai-adoption-ramps-up-80-will-be-forced-to-upskill-by-2027-as-the-profession-is-transformed/)
* [3 hours ago
    
    ### The EU wants to know more about social media algorithms – Computerworld](https://digitpatrox.com/the-eu-wants-to-know-more-about-social-media-algorithms-computerworld/)
* [4 hours ago
    
    ### Everything You Can Do With Apple’s New Passwords App](https://digitpatrox.com/everything-you-can-do-with-apples-new-passwords-app/)

Most Viewed Topics

* [August 12, 2024
    
    ### Texas Board of Physical Therapy Examiners breached, SSNs and other info compromised](https://digitpatrox.com/texas-board-of-physical-therapy-examiners-breached-ssns-and-other-info-compromised/)
* [August 28, 2024
    
    ### Getting Your iPhone Repaired Could Ban You From Snapchat](https://digitpatrox.com/getting-your-iphone-repaired-could-ban-you-from-snapchat/)
* [August 13, 2024
    
    ### How to manage a road trip move](https://digitpatrox.com/how-to-manage-a-road-trip-move/)

© Copyright 2018 - 2024, All Rights Reserved

Search for:  

close

 Search for

 Search for
